♪I want to get closer♪
♪ اريد الاقتراب ♪
♪I walk lightly♪
♪ أمشي بخفة ♪
♪Yet accidentally♪
♪ لكن بالصدفة ♪
♪Walk into your trap of love♪
♪ ادخل في فخ الحب
♪Oh no, no, no♪
♪ أوه لا ، لا ، لا
♪You cannot simply confess your love when you are drunk♪
لا يمكنك ببساطة الاعتراف بحبك وأنت في حالة سكر ♪
=Campus Ace=
= الحرم الجامعي آيس =
=Episode 23= (Get to know Unique)
= الحلقة 23 = (تعرف على الفريد)
Momo.
مومو.
You're on the campus hit list.
أنت في قائمة استهداف الحرم الجامعي.
(Tang Momo's styling: Dress well and the man will be at your door!)
(تصميم تانغ مومو: ارتدي ملابس جيدة وسيكون الرجل على بابك!)
(Comments: Please upload more. It's my kind of style. I'm following.)
(تعليقات: الرجاء تحميل المزيد. إنه نوع من أسلوبي. أنا أتابع.)
(You're so pretty. I love you. Isn't she the campus belle?)
(أنت جميلة جدا. أنا أحبك. أليست هي حسناء الحرم الجامعي؟)
(Qiao Nuanfei.)
(تشياو نوانفي.)
(Do you dare to compete with me again?)
(هل تجرؤ على التنافس معي مرة أخرى؟)
Feifei.
فايفي.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Come and help me.
تعال وساعدني.
What is this? It's so heavy.
ما هذا؟  انها ثقيلة جدا.
Clothes.
ملابس.
Clothes?
ملابس؟
Why are you buying so many clothes?
لماذا تشتري الكثير من الملابس؟
I didn't buy these.
أنا لم أشتري هذه.
Tang Momo gave them to me.
أعطاهم تانغ مومو لي.
Tang Momo?
تانغ مومو؟
Aren't you two enemies?
ألستم أعداء؟
Why did she give you clothes?
لماذا أعطتك ملابس؟
What do you know?
ماذا تعرف؟
She didn't just give me clothes.
لم تعطيني الملابس فقط.
She declared war.
أعلنت الحرب.
(Current number of people online)
(العدد الحالي للأشخاص المتصلين بالإنترنت)
Yao.
ياو.
It works.
إنها تعمل.
This is impressive!
هذا مثير للإعجاب!
It must be because of my post yesterday.
يجب أن يكون بسبب منصبي أمس.
I'm such a mediocre little marketing genius.
أنا عبقري تسويقي متوسط ​​المستوى.
Don't get too excited.
لا تتحمس كثيرا.
There are only four likes on your post.
لا يوجد سوى أربعة إبداءات الإعجاب في منشورك.
From me,
مني،
Yao,
ياو ،
Xiao'ai
شياو
and yourself.
ونفسك.
If you're a genius,
إذا كنت عبقريًا ،
then I'll be Einstein.
ثم سأكون أينشتاين.
Enough.
كافية.
Let me take a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة.
(Shocking! The two goddesses of the campus are once again competing.)
(صادم! تتنافس آلهة الحرم الجامعي مرة أخرى.)
(What is the magic of a small fashion application?)
(ما هو سحر تطبيق الموضة الصغير؟)
Look.
نظرة.
This is thanks to our spokesperson.
هذا بفضل المتحدث الرسمي لدينا.
Spokesperson?
المتحدث الرسمي؟
Momo?
مومو؟
Xiao'ai must be there, too.
يجب أن يكون Xiao'ai هناك أيضًا.
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
Han Xiao'ai.
هان شياو.
Xiao'ai did a great job at taking photos.
قام Xiao'ai بعمل رائع في التقاط الصور.
Momo looks good in these photos.
مومو تبدو جيدة في هذه الصور.
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
That's because Momo is pretty, okay?
هذا لأن مومو جميلة ، حسنًا؟
Don't you agree?
لا توافق؟
Xiao'ai took good shots.
أخذ Xiao'ai لقطات جيدة.
Our spokesperson has worked hard.
المتحدث باسمنا عمل بجد.
We can't fall far behind.
لا يمكننا أن نتخلف كثيرا.
Launch the campus belle poll now.
إطلاق استطلاع الحرم الجامعي حسناء الآن.
Get more people
احصل على المزيد من الأشخاص
to participate in this campus belle contest.
للمشاركة في مسابقة الحسناء في الحرم الجامعي.
All clear?
واضح؟
Clear!
صافي!
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Is this why
هل هذا هو السبب
you called me here?
انت اتصلت بي هنا
Will your dad agree?
هل يوافق والدك؟
I can make the decision
يمكنني اتخاذ القرار
without his consent.
دون موافقته.
You've finally toughened up.
لقد تشددت أخيرًا.
I just regret that
أنا فقط نادم على ذلك
I didn't do it earlier.
لم أفعل ذلك من قبل.
All right.
حسنا.
View the contract.
عرض العقد.
By the way,
على فكرة،
about the application issue.
حول قضية التطبيق.
I've asked someone to look into it.
لقد طلبت من شخص ما أن ينظر في الأمر.
Someone indeed
شخص ما بالفعل
stole your application
سرق تطبيقك
and presented to me.
وقدم لي.
I have fired him.
لقد طردته.
Is there any point
هل هناك أي نقطة
telling me this now?
تخبرني هذا الآن؟
Yes.
نعم.
It's true that I was oversighted
صحيح أنني كنت تحت الإشراف
and caused your loss.
وتسبب في خسارتك.
However, the application has launched online.
ومع ذلك ، تم إطلاق التطبيق عبر الإنترنت.
I can't do anything about it.
لا يمكنني فعل أي شيء حيال ذلك.
So to avoid any conflict between us,
لذلك لتجنب أي تعارض بيننا ،
I would like to
وأود أن
invite you to join us.
أدعوكم للانضمام إلينا.
I can guarantee that your right to operate Unique will remain unchanged.
يمكنني أن أضمن أن حقك في تشغيل Unique سيظل دون تغيير.
In the future,
فى المستقبل،
my brand will focus on the high-end market,
ستركز علامتي التجارية على السوق الراقية ،
while yours will focus on the affordable market.
بينما يركز لك على السوق بأسعار معقولة.
Let's work together
لنعمل معا
for mutual benefit.
من أجل المنفعة المتبادلة.
Do I have to give up on
هل علي الاستسلام
my team's hard work
العمل الشاق لفريقي
just because you say so?
فقط لأنك تقول ذلك؟
You can state your conditions.
يمكنك ذكر ظروفك.
The cost
التكلفة
is negotiable.
قابل للتفاوض.
I'll be blunt then.
سأكون صريحا بعد ذلك.
The marketing traffic,
حركة التسويق ،
data analysis
تحليل البيانات
and
و
logistics.
الخدمات اللوجستية.
Your side will be
سيكون جانبك
in charge of all these aspects.
المسؤول عن كل هذه الجوانب.
As for the cost,
بالنسبة للتكلفة ،
I want
أريد
an additional 10%.
10٪ إضافية.
Ling Yao.
لينغ ياو.
Don't go too far.
لا تذهب بعيدا.
No deal then.
لا اتفاق إذن.
Wait.
انتظر.
I agree.
أنا موافق.
(Unique Co., Ltd Signature: Ling Yao)
(توقيع شركة فريدة من نوعها ، المحدودة: لينغ ياو)
I won against you for so many years.
لقد فزت ضدك لسنوات عديدة.
I didn't expect to lose in the end.
لم أكن أتوقع الخسارة في النهاية.
Both in business
كلاهما في العمل
and love.
و الحب.
I've been thinking a lot lately.
كنت أفكر كثيرا في الآونة الأخيرة.
If only I had been braver,
لو كنت فقط أكثر شجاعة ،
then you wouldn't have gotten this far.
إذن لم تكن لتصل إلى هذا الحد.
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Because I'm braver than you.
لأنني أشجع منك.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Ling Yao!
لينغ ياو!
Where on earth are you?
اين انت على الارض
Okay.
تمام.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Sorry,
آسف،
the lady boss is calling.
رئيس سيدة الاتصال.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
Is Yao still coming?
هل مازال ياو قادم؟
The soup is boiling.
الحساء يغلي.
No, we can't start without him.
لا ، لا يمكننا البدء بدونه.
He said he'd be here soon.
قال إنه سيكون هنا قريبًا.
Why don't we eat first?
لماذا لا نأكل أولا؟
I agree.
أنا موافق.
Wait. How could you?
انتظر.  كيف استطعت؟
Just wait a little longer.
فقط انتظر قليلا
How can we celebrate
كيف نحتفل
without the boss?
بدون رئيس؟
Let's wait for him.
دعنا ننتظره.
Good.
جيد.
You're here.
أنت هنا.
What took you so long?
ما الذي أخرك؟
We've been waiting for you.
كنا في انتظارك.
You're finally here.
أنت هنا أخيرًا.
Dig in.
حفر في.
Let's eat.
لنأكل.
Eat tofu.
أكل التوفو.
We were waiting for you.
كنا في انتظاركم.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Eat it while it's hot.
تناولها وهي ساخنة.
(Annual Gala) Congratulation,
(حفل سنوي) مبروك ،
(Invitation to Crabapple Award) my little designer.
(دعوة إلى جائزة Crabapple) مصممي الصغير.
How come?
كيف ذلك؟
Did you submit my sketches?
هل قدمت رسوماتي؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Don't just eat vegetables. Have some meat.
لا تأكل الخضار فقط.  تناول بعض اللحوم.
Eat more meat.
تناول المزيد من اللحوم.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
I want to eat meat.
اريد ان اكل اللحم.
Let me take it for you.
اسمحوا لي أن آخذه من أجلك.
Put more meat.
ضعي المزيد من اللحوم.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
It's so hot.
انه حار جدا.
Take something to eat.
خذ شيئًا لتأكله.
Let me put more meat for you.
اسمحوا لي أن أضع المزيد من اللحوم لك.
Eat this.
كل هذا.
Hello, mother.
مرحبا امي.
Here. Talk to your son.
هنا.  تحدث إلى ابنك.
I don't want to talk to him.
لا اريد التحدث معه.
You go ahead.
تفضل.
Your dad
والدك
is stubborn.
عنيد.
He brags about your application every day
يتفاخر بطلبك كل يوم
and tells people that his son runs it.
ويخبر الناس أن ابنه يديرها.
Ling Yao.
لينغ ياو.
Stop bickering with your dad.
توقف عن المشاحنات مع والدك.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Come home for a meal some day.
تعال إلى المنزل لتناول وجبة في يوم من الأيام.
Bring Momo with you.
أحضر مومو معك.
Okay.
تمام.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
What did your mother say?
ماذا قالت والدتك؟
My mother said
امي قالت
it's time for the ugly daughter-in-law to go back and meet her in-laws.
حان الوقت لكي تعود زوجة ابنها القبيحة وتلتقي بأهل زوجها.
You're the ugly one.
أنت القبيح.
You are the ugliest.
أنت أبشع.
♪Hey, do not blink at me♪
♪ مهلا ، لا ترمش في وجهي
♪I don't want♪
♪ لا أريد ♪
Speaking of this,
بالحديث عن هذا ،
even the ugly daughter-in-law has the chance to meet her in-laws,
حتى زوجة الابن القبيحة لديها الفرصة لمقابلة أهلها ،
when will I get my turn?
متى سآخذ دوري؟
Hua.
منتج.
You want to be an ugly daughter-in-law?
تريد أن تكون زوجة ابن قبيحة؟
♪You always sigh♪
♪ أنت دائمًا تتنهد ♪
Eat up.
أكل.
Let's drink to
دعونا نشرب
two ugly daughters-in-law!
ابنتا ابنتان قبيحتان!
Cheers!
هتافات!
♪You love bumping into her♪
♪ أنت تحب الاصطدام بها
♪On every sunny day♪
♪ في كل يوم مشمس
♪Approach gently♪
♪ اقترب برفق ♪
♪My letter of love confession♪
♪ رسالتي اعتراف بالحب ♪
♪I chat shyly with her♪
♪ أتحدث معها بخجل ♪
♪While avoiding her gaze♪
مع تجنب نظرتها ♪
♪I predict our destiny♪
♪ أتوقع مصيرنا ♪
♪We are not lovers yet♪
♪ لسنا عشاق بعد ♪